<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="MetaWare IDE New Project Tutorial">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/mw_w_queens.htm">
      <description>
         Welcome to the MetaWare IDE New Project Tutorial.
			This tutorial will help you understand how to create a new project and have the MetaWare IDE manage your entire build environment. 
			<br/>

      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Create a Project" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?2">
      <description>
         Create a C/C++ project by selecting the menu item:<br/>
			 File &gt; New &gt; C Project.
         You now see the New Project wizard.			 
      </description>
   </item>
      <item title="Name Your Project" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?4">
         <description>
            Enter a name (such as HelloWorld) for the project. 
   			You can also enter a new path for your project by deselecting the Use Default Location checkbox and entering the new path in the Directory: text box.
   
   			Don't click Next until you've chosen a project type and toolchain.

         </description>
   </item>      

      <item title="Select a Project Type" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?4">
         <description>
                     Choose a project type:<br/> <br/> 
	             Executable<br/>
	             Shared library<br/>
	             Static library<br/>
	             Makefile - Empty project for importing existing makefile-based projects.<br/><br/> 
	             For this tutorial, choose Executable. Don't click Next until you choose a toolchain.
	    				

         
         </description>
      </item>
         <item title="Select a Toolchain" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/mw_w_queens.htm">
            <description>
               Click a toolchain in the Toolchain box.
               The default is ARC4 for ARCtangent-A4. For other ARC targets, choose ARCompact. Later you can further specify your exact ARCompact-based processor. 
               <br/>After you click Next, the Select Configurations dialog appears.			
            </description>
         </item>
      <item title="Select Your Configurations" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?6">
         <description>
            Configurations describe the build settings for your executable, since you probably want different settings for debugging and release. You can even create your own configuration. 
            For this tutorial, accept the defaults and click Advanced settings....
            <br/>The Properties dialog for your project appears. 
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="View the Properties Dialog" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/mw_t_set_build_opts.htm">
         <description>
   	In the Properties dialog you can change default settings for your project. 
   	Expand C/C++ Build and select Settings.      
   	</description>
      </item>
      <item title="Specify the Tool Settings" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/mw_t_set_build_opts.htm">
         <description>
   	In the Properties dialog you can change default settings for your project. 
   	Expand C/C++ Build and select Settings. For ARCompact, select Processor/Extensions and
   	select your exact ARC Core Version from the drop-down list.
   	</description>
      </item>
         <item title="Exit the Properties Dialog" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/mw_t_set_build_opts.htm">
            <description>
      	In an actual project, you can make other selections as well. 
      	For now, click OK. <br/>
      	Your new project appears in the Project Explorer.
      	</description>
         </item>
      <item title="Create a File" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/cdt_t_new_cpp.htm">
         <description>
            Create a new C file by right-clicking your project and selecting New &gt; File.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="Use the New File Wizard" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/cdt_t_new_cpp.htm">
         <description>
            The New File wizard appears.<br/>
   
   			Enter the name of your file (such as hello.c) in the File name: text area, and click Finish.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="View the New Project File" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/mw_w_queens.htm">
         <description>
            The new file is visible under your project in the Project Explorer, and is open in the Editor view.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="Enter Code" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/cdt_t_new_cpp.htm">
         <description>
            Enter the code in the hello.c file that you created. You can double click the hello.c tab in the Editor view to expand the view.
   			<br/>			
   			Notice the asterisk left of the file name on the tab. The asterisk indicates that the file has changed but has not been saved.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="Step Through the Code" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?12">
         <description>
            Notice that the Outline view is now populated with objects created from your code.
   			<br/>
   			If you select an item from the Outline view, the corresponding code is highlighted in the editor.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="Save the File" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_basic.htm?13">
         <description>
            Now save the hello.c file by clicking File &gt; Save, and build your project by typing Ctrl+b.
   			<br/>
   			You can read through the build messages in the Console view. When the project builds successfully, the Console view shows the following message:
   			<br/>
   			Finished building target: hello.elf
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="View the Executable" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/reference/cdt_u_project_explorer_view.htm">
         <description>
            Expand the Binaries item under your project in the Project Explorer. You now see the executable ELF file listed.
         </description>
      </item>
      <item title="Run the Application" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/reference/cdt_u_m_run.htm">
         <description>
            You can run your application within the C/C++ Perspective. To do so click Run &gt; Run...<br/>
            Your file runs to completion. The Console view displays the output.
   	</description>
      </item>
</cheatsheet>
