<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<cheatsheet title="Standard Make Tutorial">
	<intro
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm">
		<description>
			Welcome to the MetaWare IDE Standard Make tutorial.
			Running through this tutorial will help you understand how to create a new project 
			and have the MetaWare IDE use the makefile within your build environment!
		</description>
	</intro>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?2"
		title="Create a Project">
		<description>
			Create a C/C++ project by selecting the menu item File &gt; New &gt; Standard Make C Project.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?3"
		title="New Project Wizard">
		<description>
			The New Project wizard starts.<br/> 
			Enter a project name, such as HelloWorld, for the new project. 
			<br/>
			You can also enter a new path for your project by deselecting the &quot;Use Default&quot; 
			checkbox and entering the new path in the Directory: text box. Click Next.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?5"
		title="Project Settings">
		<description>
			The Projects tab appears first. Here you can select other referenced C/C++ projects. 
			Because this is a simple Hello World project, you do not need to make any selections 
			here. <br/>Click Next.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?6"
		title="Make Builder">
		<description>
			Click the Make Builder tab. Note that the MetaWare Development Toolkit uses gmake, which 
			is selected by default.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?7"
		title="Error Parsers">
		<description>
			Click the Error Parsers tab. Here you can select the error parsers you require for a project 
			and change the order in which error parsers are called. For this tutorial, you can leave all
			parsers selected.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?8"
		title="Binary Parser">
		<description>
			Click the Binary Parser tab and select the binary parsers you require for the project. You 
			can also change the order in which binary parsers are called. For this tutorial, you can leave 
			only the ELF Parser selected.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?9"
		title="Discovery Options">
		<description>
			Click the Discovery Options tab. This tab defines the configuration for autodiscovery of 
			include paths and preprocessor symbols for the parser to enable the parser to understand 
			the contents of the C/C++ source code. This helps you more effectively use the search and 
			code completion features. Make sure ARC C/C++ Compiler Specs Parser is selected under 
			&quot;Command output parser&quot;.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?10"
		title="C/C++ Indexer">
		<description>
			You can enable or disable the C/C++ Indexer here. The indexer is necessary for search and 
			related features, like content assist and refactoring. While there may be situations where 
			the indexer is not required, for this project you can leave it enabled.
			<br/>
			When you have completed setting your C/C++ project preferences, click Finish. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?11"
		title="New Project">
		<description>
			You should now see the new project in the C/C++ Projects view. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?12"
		title="Create a Makefile">
		<description>
			Create the makefile by right-clicking your project and selecting New > File. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?13"
		title="New File Wizard">
		<description>
			You now see the New File wizard.
			<br/>
			Enter makefile as the name of the file in the File name text box, and click Finish. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?14"
		title="New Makefile">
		<description>
			You now see the empty makefile in the Projects view under the project, and makefile 
			is open in the Editor view. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?15"
		title="Enter the Make Script">
		<description>
			Enter the build instruction for the makefile you just created. The Outline view updates 
			to display the structure of the makefile as you add components. When you enter the code, 
			note the asterisk in front of the file name on the tab in the Editor view. The asterisk 
			tells you the file was changed but has not been saved.
			<br/>
			<b>Note:</b> Ensure you have tabs, not spaces, before your indented code, as gmake does not 
			accept spaces before commands.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?16"
		title="Create a C File">
		<description>
			Create the hello.c file by right-clicking your project and selecting New > File.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?17"
		title="New File Wizard">
		<description>
			The New File wizard appears.
			<br/>
			Enter hello.c in the File name text box and click Finish.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?18"
		title="New C File">
		<description>
			&quot;hello.c&quot; is now listed in the Projects view under the project, and the empty file is open in 
			the Editor view.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?19"
		title="Enter Code">
		<description>
			Enter the code in the hello.c file you just created. You can double-click the hello.c tab in 
			the Editor view to expand the view.
			<br/>
			Note the asterisk in the Editor tab next to each filename. It indicates that changes to 
			the file have not yet been saved.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?20"
		title="Build the Project">
		<description>
			By default, your project is built on save. To build, save the files by selecting File &gt; Save All or pressing Ctrl+Shift+S.
			<br/>
			If you disabled &quot;Build automatically&quot;, you can build manually by selecting Project &gt; Build All (Ctrl+b).
			<br/>
			Read through the build messages in the Console view. If any errors occurred, you can see them in the Problems view.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?21"
		title="Run the Application">
		<description>
			The executable is now listed in the C/C++ Projects view with all other files in the project.
			<br/>
			You can run your application within the C/C++ perspective by creating a "run configuration." To do so, select Run &gt; Run....
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?22"
		title="Run Configuration">
		<description>
			The initial Run dialog appears. Make sure C/C++ Local Application is selected in the Configurations: view, and click New.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?23"
		title="New Configuration">
		<description>
			Make sure HelloWorld is selected in the Configurations: view and click the Main tab. This is where you select your C/C++ application and other settings that will impact how your application is run.
			<br/>
			If the program is not specified, click Search and locate HelloWorld.elf. 
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?24"
		title="Manage Configuration">
		<description>
			HelloWorld.elf now appears in the C/C++ Application:  text box. The other tabs allow you to make additional settings. For the tutorial, accept the defaults.
			<br/>
			Click Run to run the application.
		</description>
	</item>
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/getting_started/cdt_w_standard.htm?25"
		title="Console View">
		<description>
			Output from the application appears in the Console view.
			<br/>
			If your project contains multiple applications, the title bar of the Console view shows which application is running.
			<br/>
			Because HelloWorld is a short application, it runs to completion.			
		</description>
	</item>
</cheatsheet>